realgirlsgonebad.com 2017-06-06

# RealGirlsGoneBad.com - No fakes, No actresses, just real girls gone bad

**_Privacy Policy_**

RealGirlsGoneBad (“RGGB”) recognises that your privacy is important to you. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to your use of www.realgirlsgonebad.com (the “Site”), as well as any of the content, services, products, software and applications offered by RGGB (the “Services”).

This Privacy Policy summarises RGGB’s privacy practices and the uses of the information that RGGB gathers via the Site and the Services.

Please note that RGGB may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you should check this page periodically for changes. If changes are made, RGGB will notify users by stating the date the Privacy Policy change is effective. If significant changes to the Privacy Policy are made, it will be prominently indicated on the Site.

 **The Information which RGGB Collects and Uses**

In connection with your access to or use of the Site and/or the Services, RGGB may request and/or collect from you personal information that may include: first and last name, address, phone number, email address, location or other information (“Personal Information”).

By accessing or using the Site or the Services you are accepting the terms of RGGB’s Privacy Policy.

 **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE PRIVACY PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE RGGB SITE OR SERVICES.**

 **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

RGGB may use the Personal Information collected for the following purposes:

•  providing, analysing, personalising or improving the Site or the Services

•  communicating with you in general, including to provide information about the Site and the Services

•  enabling RGGB to publish content to the Site

•  developing new services

•  measuring interest in and improving the Site or the Service

•  notifying you about special offers and products or services available from RGGB that may be of interest to you

•  otherwise customising your user experience with RGGB

•  soliciting information from you, including through surveys

•  resolving disputes or troubleshooting problems

•  preventing potentially prohibited or illegal activities

•  enforcing our Terms of Use, and/or

•  as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

We may collect information about your computer for system administration, including where available: your IP address, operating system and browser type. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

 **Sharing of Information**

RGGB does not share Personal Information with other companies or individuals except in the following limited circumstances:

•  When we have your consent.

•  We may provide such Personal Information to affiliated companies or other trusted businesses for the purposes of processing Personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

•  RGGB may request additional information from you in online forms. Such forms may require you to provide contact information (such as your name and postal address). Information that you provide may be used for (without limitation) billing and accounting purposes. RGGB may also use any contact information which you provide to communicate with you about, products or services.

•  RGGB may partner with other third parties to provide specific goods or services. When you register to receive information for such goods or services, RGGB will share names or other contact information that is necessary for that third party to provide these goods or services. RGGB does not authorise third party providers to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose related to these goods or services.

RGGB may disclose your Personal Information when access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to

•  satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request

•  enforce applicable Terms of Use including investigation of potential violations thereof

•  detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues, or

•  protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of RGGB, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

When you send email or other communications to RGGB, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve the Site and the Services.

RGGB may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information to a buyer or transferee of all or a portion of its assets in conjunction with the sale or transfer of such assets; however, we will provide notice on our web site before Personal Information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

 **Session Logging**

When you access the Site or the Services, RGGB’s servers may automatically track certain information about your use of the Site and the Services. This information may include your browser type and version, your IP address, any referring URL, any URLs you visit from the Site, and the time and date associated with, and the content of, any communications by, to or with the Site or the Services.

 **Cookies, Advertising and Links to other Web sites**

When you use the Site, a cookie may be sent to your browser. A cookie is a small text file sent by a website’s computer system that is stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are a commonly used technology on the Web, and they are used in the Site’s functionality.

If you register with us or if you continue to use the Site, you agree to our use of cookies.

You are always free to set your browser to decline cookies, and you can delete cookies from your computer. However, disabling cookies may adversely affect your ability to use the Site or the Services. See your browser’s “Help” file for more details on cookies.

Cookies may be used to recognise you, as well as to track usage of the Site. These cookies are stored on your computer’s hard drive, and help to establish usage trends and to tailor website content and develop further enhancements. Advertisers and other third parties and/or affiliates’ use of cookies are subject to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to read those privacy policies.

The Site and the Services may contain windows or hyperlinks which provide access to other websites not affiliated with RGGB. Your use of an external website or any informational content found on an external website is subject to and governed by the terms and guidelines of that external website.

RGGB does not make any representations or warranties concerning, and will not in any way be liable for, any content, products, services, software, or other materials available on an external website, even if one or more pages of the external website are framed within a page of the Site.

RGGB is not responsible for the privacy practices of any external website. For your protection, please refer to the privacy policies of the respective external websites.

 **Our Commitment to Data Security**

To improve data security and restrict access to your personal and business information, RGGB has put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information which we collect through the Site.

RGGB does not, however, guarantee that information collected via the Site is or will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or from other dishonest or criminal activities, or in the event of a failure of computer hardware, software, or a telecommunications network.

 **Compromise of Personal Information**

In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a known or suspected breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures contained in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

 **Notification Procedures**

It is RGGB’s policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to our users via e-mail notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Site, as determined by us in our sole discretion.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to our web site users.

 **Deletion or Modification of Personal Information**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.

We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes.

You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting us at info@realgirlsgonebad.com.

Effective Date: May 1st 2012
